United Housing Foundation Files 6129
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Housing Foundation Files
1953-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Housing Foundation
6129
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Records.
5811560
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
MValadez, October 12, 2004
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The United Housing Foundation was founded in 1950 by the existing consumer cooperative housing organizations. Its purpose was to provide assistance to new groups of people who might wish to organize or join a cooperative. In order to maintain the organization, membership of labor unions and other non-profit groups that were interested in helping to provide better housing was encouraged. Investments from those groups, including the State Division of Housing, made moderate-cost housing possible.
The work that has been initiated and sponsored by the United Housing Foundation includes slum clearance and many redevelopment projects. By using private capital, they have been able to replace slum dwellings with moderately priced modern housing. During its first ten years, the United Housing Foundation initiated or sponsored housing cooperatives in New York City such as Seward Park Housing Corp., ILGWU Houses at Penn Station South, and Rochdale Village at the Jamaica Race Track. Rochdale Village is the largest cooperative sponsored by the United Housing Foundation with almost 6,000 housing units.
Scope and Contents
Photographs, contact sheets, and negatives. Includes construction, groundbreaking and moving in, meetings, and community activities of various Co-Ops arranged in alphabetical order.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Housing, Cooperative--New York (State)--New York; United Housing Foundation (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union -- Archives; United Housing Foundation (New York, N.Y.) --Archives
5811560
- Albany 3/23/71 (contact + neg), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Dwellings Annual Meeting 5/6/71 (contact + neg), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bell Park Gardens, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  John F. Kennedy Circle
- Bell Park Manor and Terrace, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bronx Consumers Cooperative Society (-A.H. consumers) (1), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  buildings and architecture
- Bronx Consumers Cooperative Society (-A.H. consumers) (2), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bronx Consumers Cooperative Society (-A.H. consumers) (3), 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bronx Consumers Cooperative Society (4), 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chelsea Co-Op Supermarket (1), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Sam Weiss: photographer
- Chelsea Co-Op Supermarket (2), 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Consumers Assembly 5/1/71 (contact + negatives), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Co-Op City Application Office, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Photos
- Co-Op City Banker's Visit. State Division of Housing, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Co-Op City: Community Activities (1), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Co-Op City Community Activities (2), 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Co-Op City Community Activities 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Co-Op City: Day Camp, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Co-Op City: Document Signings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Co-Op City: Drawings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Co-Op City: Educational Park Groundbreaking 10/28/68, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Co-Op City Grounds and Buildings 1972, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Co-Op City: Groundbreaking (press file), 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Co-Op City: Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Co-Op City: Memorial for Dr. King 4/7/68, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Co-Op City: Moving In, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Co-Op City: Model and Site Plan, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Co-Op City: Occupied, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Co-Op City: Organizations, Clubs, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Co-Op City: Personnel, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Co-Op City: Power plant, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Co-Op City: "Progress Report + Inspection" 5/12/67 (1), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Co-Op City: "Progress Report + Inspection" 5/12/67 (2), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Co-Op: Quality Education Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Co-Op City: Rock Festival (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Don Martin Lecture (contact + neg) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- French Visitors + Mssrs (contact + neg) Schechter + Jessor (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Grand St. Market Meeting 5/26/71 (negative), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Iowa Listening Session: Statler Hilton 5/4/71 (contact + neg), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Mid-Eastern By Laws Meeting, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Technical Services Contact Sheet + Photos (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Penn South, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Penn South Community Activities, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Penn South Buildings, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Penn South Fifth Anniversary (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Penn South Moving In (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Penn South Hearings and Signings, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Penn South Relocation, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- People In Supermarkets, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Rochdale Center 6/13/71 (contacts + neg), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Rochdale Consumes Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Rochdale Consumer's Cooperative Society Opening, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Rochdale Co-Op Market, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Rochdale, England (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Rochdale Institute (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Rochdale Pharmacy, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  33 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Power Plant Construction #1, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  48 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Power Plant Construction #2, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  37 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Power Plant Construction #3, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  24 Photographs
- Rochdale Village, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  47 Photographs
- Rochdale Village, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  28 Photographs
- Rochdale Village Aerial view, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  6 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Aerial View Construction #1, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  15 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Aerial View Construction #2, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Rochdale Village: Areas for School Construction, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  3 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Concert Series, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  31 Photograph
- Rochdale Village Construction 1961-1962 #1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Rochdale Village: Constrction 1961-1962 #2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  29 Photographs
- Rochdale Village Constructon 1961-1962 #3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  23 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Construction 1963 #1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  30 Photographs
- Rochdale Village Construction 1963 #2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  49 Photographs
- Rochdale Village Construction 1963 #3 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  32 Photographs
- Rochdale Community Activities #1, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Over 100 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Community Activities #2, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  61 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Community Activities #3, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  82 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Community Singers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  2 Photographs
- Rochdale village Day Camp, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Rochdale Village: Election, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Rochdale Village Hearings, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  10 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Jamaica Race Track, Demolition, etc., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Rochdale Village: Move-in Period, Auditorium, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  3 Photograph
- Rochdale Village Racetrack, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  11 Photographs
- Rochdale village: Rochdale Players, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  7 Photographs
- Rochdale Village: Site Plans, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  11 Photograph
- Senior Citizen Demo (Contact + Neg), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  50 Photographs
- Seward Park Market Meeting 5/27/71 (Contacts + Neg), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  5 Negative Photographs
- Shapiro, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  4 Photographs, 3 Negative Photographs, 7 total
- Twin Pines Village (Press Conference) 6/27/67 #1, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  58 Photographs
- Twin Pines Village (Press Conference) 6/27/67 #2, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Twin Pines Village (Press Conference) 6/27/67 #3, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  32 Photographs, 6 Negatives, 38 total
- United Housing foundation (U.H.F.) Annual Meetings, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  4 Photographs
- U.H.F. Annual Meeting 1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  17 Photograph
- U.H.F. Annual Meeting 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  19 Photographs
- U.H.F. Annual Meetings 1964, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  43 Photographs
- U.H.F. Annual Meeting 5/18/67, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  71 Photographs
- U.H.F Annual Meeting 1970 #1 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  114 Photograph
- U.H.F. Annual Meeting 1970 #2 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  99 Photographs
- United Housing Foundation (U.H.F.) Contact Sheets Annual Meeting 1972 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  5 Neg. Sheets
- United housing Foundation 20th Anniversary (U.H.F.) Dinner Dance, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  42 Photographs, 2 Neg. Sheets, 44 total
- U.H.F. Management and Services, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  87 Photographs
- Unlabeled Contact Sheets., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  6 Neg. Sheets
- Unlabeled Photos, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  5 Photographs
- Unlabelled Photos. (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Unlabeled Contact Sheets + Photo (Box 2, Folder 49)
  1 Photograph, 10 Neg. sheets, 11 total
- Unlabeled Photos, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  9 Photographs
- Apt. Applications Waiting List #1, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Apt. Applications Waiting List #2, 1958-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Board Meeting #1, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Board Meeting #2, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Board Meeting #3, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Board Meeting #4, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Commercial tenants, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Community Activities, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Dedication, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- I.L.G.W.U., 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Members - Meetings and Mailings #1, 1958-1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Members - Meetings and Mailings 32, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Members - Meetings and Mailings #3, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cooperators Corresp. - 1963 #1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cooperators corresp. - 1963 #2 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cooperators Corresp. - 1963 #3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Project Description, 1957-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Protestant Episcopal Church, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- U.H.F., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Publicity, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Minute Book U.H.F. March 1971, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Minute Book Community Services, Inc. 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Community Services, Inc. Minute Book, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- United Housing Foundation Minute Book, 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Coordinated Hsg. Service Board Minutes, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Mut. Housing Assn. - 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Mut. Housing Assn. - 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Mut. Housing Assn. 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Mut. Housing Assn., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Mut. Housing Assn., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Mutual Housing Assn. 1958-1959 - Other (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Mutual Housing Assn. 1958-1959 Annual Reports (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Mutual Housing Association - 1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Mutual Housing Association Corresp. 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Annual & Stockholders Meetings - UHF, CS, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Apartment Requesta, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bd. Of Directors - UHF, CS 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Bd. Of Directors - UHF, CS 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Member Organizations, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Publications - 1966 #1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Publications - 1966 #2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Publications - 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Annual Meeting 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Board Minutes 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Corresp. Member Organizations, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Community Services Inc., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Board Members 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Annual Meeting 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Correspondence Board Members, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Member Organizations, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Regular Meeting Board of Directors United Housing Foundation, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Community Services Inc., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Meetings - Annual and Misc. 1972-74, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Meetings - UHF - CS Ann. & Misc. '77-78, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Members - Mlings & Misc. Corr. 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Bd. Of Directors - UHF - CS 1975-78, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- UHF - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- UHF - 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- UHF - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- UHF - 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Bd of Directors UHF-CS 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- 1974 Annual Meeting (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Correspondence Member Organizations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Board Minutes, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Community Services, Inc., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Annual Meeting 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Board Members, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Apt. Applications - 1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Apt. Applications 1962-65, 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Apt. Applications - Statistics, 1957-1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Bd. Of Directors, 1961-1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Cooperators Corresp 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Cooperators Corrsp. - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Cooperators Corresp. 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Members - Mailings Meetings 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Members - Mailings Meetings 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Members - Mailings Meetings 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- W - Board of Director, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- W - Cooperators Correspondence, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Project Description, 1957-1964 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Publicity 1957-1966 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Site, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Robert Owen Houses, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Project Description, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Bowery Quadrangle, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Apt. Application Requests, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Applicants Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- A.E. Kazan 1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Community Activities, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Publicity, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated 30 Year Report, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Site, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- A.E. Kazan 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Harold Ostroff 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Publicity, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous - UHF Jan. - April 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Publications, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Bd. Of Directors - UHF, CS - 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- W - Board of Directors 1968 #1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- W - Board of Directors 1968 #2 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- W - Apt. Applications, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- W - Board of Directors 1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Seward Park Housing Corp. - 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Seward Park Housing Corporation Year Ended, November 30, 1965
- Seward Park Brochure (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Some Pertinent Facts ABOUT HOUSING COOPERATIVE and PROSPECTUS ON SEWARD PARK HOUSING. COMMUNITY SERVICES, INC. 530 GRAND STREET NYC
- Co-Op Village - Apt. Applns. 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  correspondence
- Park Reservoir Correspondence 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Szold & Bandwen, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Szold, Brandwen, Meyers & Blumberg
- Bd. Meetings, Memos, 1956-1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Publicity 1956-1963, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Newspapers
- Community Services, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Herman Jesser, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Herman Jessor - architect
- Members - Mailings, Meetings, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Members - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Project Description, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Rochdale Village Invitations, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Publicity 1964-66, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Rochdale Consumers - Reports, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Rochdale Consumers - Financial Reports, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Rochdale Consumers - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Rochdale Consumers - Financial Reports #2, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Rochdale Consumers - Minutes, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Rochdale Misc. 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Rochdale Village - Minutes, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Rochdale Village - Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Rochdale Village MGR's Report, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Rochdale Village - Other Reports, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Rochdale Village - By-Laws, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Mutual Housing - Minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Mutual Housing - Financial Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Mutual Housing - Other, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Riverbay Consumers - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Riverbay Consumers - By-Laws, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Riverbay Consumers - Financial Report, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Riverbay Consumers - Other, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Riverbay Corp. - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Riverbay Corp. - Financial Report, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Riverbay Corp. - Other Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Riverbay Corp. - By-Laws, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Riverbay Consumers - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Riverbay Consumers - Financial Report, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Riverday Consumers - Other Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Riverbay Consumers - Misc. #1, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Riverbay Consumers - Misc. #2, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Riverbay Consumers - Misc. #3, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Riverbay No. 1 - Report, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Riverbay No. 1 - Financial Reports (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Riverbay No. 1 - Financial Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Riverbay No. 1 - Minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- CONTRACT: Seward Park Housing Corp., 1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Agreement Between The City of New York And Seward Park Housing Corporation. September 19, 1957
- Grand Street Consumers Cooperative, Inc, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Mr. Ostroff; Reports, Financial Reports, Minutes, Bylaws.
- Seward Park Consumers Cooperation, Inc, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Annual Report 1969; reports; financial reports; by-laws
- Amalgamated-Warbasse Houses, Inc, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Minutes; Financial reports; Manager's report; other reports; res. Fund
- Warbasse Consumers Cooperative Society, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  reports(none); financial reports(none); minutes; by-laws
- Park Reservoir Housing Corps, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Minutes; others; by-laws
- Rochdale Village Inc, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  by-laws; minutes; financial report; manager's report; other reports
- Consumer Assembly: Mutual Housing, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  by-laws; minutes; other; mutual housing
- Rochdale Consumers Cooperative Society, Inc, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  reports; financial reports; by-laws; minutes
- Riverbay Corp. #1, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Riverbay Corp. #2, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Riverbay Corp. #2, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Riverbay Corp. #3, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Riverbay Corp. Manager Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Riverbay Corp. Financial Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Riverbay Corp. Other Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Rochdale Village No. 2 - Intro., 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Rochdale Village No. 2 - By-Laws, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Rochdale Village No. 2 - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Rochdale Village No. 2 - Other, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Warbasse, 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Warbasse Manager's Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Warbasse Reserve Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Warbasse Financial Report & By- Laws, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Rochdale Village Inc. - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Rochdale Village Inc. - Financial Reports #1, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Rochdale Village Inc. Financial Reports #2, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Co-op Contact Vols. 1 through 4; 1955 through 1960, 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Co-Op Contact, 1961-1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Co-Op Contact 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Co-Op Contact 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- N.Y.C. Housing Authority, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Co-Op Contact 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Co-Op Contact Issues; 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Community Services Inc. - Financial Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Community Service Inc. - Minutes, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Community Service Inc. - Other Reports, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Community Services Inc. By-Laws, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Community Services Inc. Financial Report #2, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Community Service Inc. - Minutes, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Community Services Inc. - Other Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Park Reservoir - Minutes, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Park Reservoir - Financial Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Park Reservoir - Other, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Minutes Book United Housing Foundation April 8, 1960 to June 23, 1964, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Minutes book United Housing Foundation December 31, 1964 to January 5, 1967, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- U.H.F. Inc., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- U.H.F. 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Mutual Redevelopment Houses, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Federation of Cooperatives, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)